hetmanrecovery.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy for HetmanRecovery.com Visitors

Hetman Software makes your privacy a top priority. This document discloses the collection, use, and storage of personal information by Hetman Software and https://hetmanrecovery.com/ (hereinafter referred to as “Web site”) visitors.

## GDPR

Effective May 25th, 2018, if you are from the European Economic Area (“EEA”), our processing of your personal data will comply with the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).

To request access to, correction or deleting of your personal data, you may use our online form or send an e-mail located at this page.

## Cookies and Visitor Tracking

The Web site collects anonymous information about the visitors by using cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer for a pre-defined period of time. The use of cookies allows us to determine visitors’ path on our Web site, optimize the content and streamline Web site structures. In addition, cookies allow us to determine first-time and repeat visitors. Cookies set by Hetman Software contain no personal information.

You have full control over cookies set by Hetman Software. Modern Web browsers such as Mozilla, Chrome, Safari or Internet Explorer provide means to control the handling of cookies on your computer. You may block all future cookies, clear and delete existing ones at your will. Please note that if you disable cookies, certain minor functionality of our Web site may not be available to you due to technical limitations. By visiting Hetman Software, you agree to the use of cookies by Hetman Software as regulated by this Privacy Policy.

Our Web site uses Google Analytics, a Web site traffic analysis application provided by Google. The use of cookies by Google Analytics is governed by Google’s own Privacy Policy.

Google Analytics collects anonymous information about visitors to our Web site and their behavior on our online property. Information collected by Google Analytics may include (but is not limited to) referrer data, visitor’s IP address, Web pages visited, and time spent on our Web site. This information is stored exclusively on Google servers, and is governed by Google [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/ "Google: Privacy Policy"). We at Hetman Software use this information to optimize our Web site to improve its performance, usability and content.

## The Use of Personal Information

Hetman Software does not sell, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties except when required by international and local laws and government regulations.

## Software Registration

When purchasing a license to our software, you will provide certain personally identifiable information such as your name, email and mailing address, as well as any financial information required to process your payment. This information is provided to our authorized resellers including PayProGlobal, Softkey, AllSoft, and is used according to their respective Privacy Policies. Registration information required to unlock all features of Hetman products is delivered to you by email. By using these registration credentials you agree to the receipt of this email.

## Physical Media Delivery

If you are ordering our software delivered on a physical media, you will need to supply your mailing address. By ordering the delivery of physical media, you automatically agree to be sent a sending to your specified delivery address.

## Personal Information

We do not have access to your financial information. We do not solicit your personal information, and do not ask for or collect information about the age of our visitors. If we get aware of holding information about a minor under the age of 13, we’ll take every step to destroy such information as soon as possible.

## Other Web Sites

Our Web site may contain links to external resources that belong to Hetman Software or third parties. These resources are governed by their own respective Privacy Policies. When following these links, make sure to review these Web sites’ respective Privacy Policies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to change, modify or revoke this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. We shall post any changes to the Privacy Policy on this Web page. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please make sure to contact us directly.
